<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meeting Notes on Pralay -- The Climate Game</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meeting Notes on Pralay -- The Climate Game</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2024 </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2024-10-23 Meeting Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-23/</guid>
      <description>Agenda # Create backstory for main character– history, motivation, some form of character arc, what happens in the end Work on story structure (eg: Harmon&amp;rsquo;s story circle, Field&amp;rsquo;s act structure, Uninhabitable Earth chapter Initiate work on game scenarios– figure out number, increase in intensity; divide work between ourselves Create a PoA for online meetings in the coming days Abhishek: Aesthetics survey Abhishek and Tanvi: Meeting notes From survey– Thematic analysis of textual responses Clean data Naamkaran # Names for factions– Providers: Varutri (coverer, guardian) or Prakrit (natural, nature-related) Imperials: Aalim (learned) or Lalit (pure/untarnished) Aspirants: Trushna (thirst) or Yatharth (reality) Online PoA # Meet at 1030 everyday on Discord to discuss individual assignments Meet at 1800 everyday on Discore to go over work that everyone Extensively document research/notes that are individually taken on story doc At the end of each day, one person summarises and adds notes to website Work to be divided includes Game scenarios Survey analysis Main Character Syndrome- # Main character from T-Y.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-09-20 Meeting Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-09-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-09-20/</guid>
      <description>We met to set an agenda for our Office Hours with the ELM team and chart out our next steps with secondary research For ELM Office Hours on 2024-09-21: # Problem statement– refined and finalised with SMART characteristics in mind 5 success and failure points identified based on literature review across SciComm, BehSci, Gaming, ClimSci Finalizing on game content– number of scenarios, time spent, weight given to decisions - maybe consult a game expert on this before we start?</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-09-21 | Day&#39;s Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-09-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-09-21/</guid>
      <description>Office Hour with ELM Supervisors # Anushka, Tanvi, Shweata, and Abhishek summarized their respective literature reviews Feedback # Srikant&amp;rsquo;s suggestion: Be brutal with your marketing.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-10-01 Interview with Sayan Chaudhari</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-01/</guid>
      <description>We met with Sayan Chaudhari, a Critical Writing Faculty with the YIF at Ashoka University.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-10-03 | Meeting with Dr Alexander Philips </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-03/</guid>
      <description>We met Dr Alexander Philips, an English Professor at Ashoka University after discovering he teaches a course called Climate Fiction.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-10-17 Meeting Notes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-17/</guid>
      <description>Abhishek, Anushka, and Tanvi met for a quick meeting around setting up work to be presented during Office Hours with the ELM team and charting out our next steps during the immersion week Hypothesis Generation # We set up three hypotheses that came out of our secondary research and stakeholder interaction H1 – People who play the game will perform better on the post game survey than those who don&amp;rsquo;t play the game H2 – People with prior knowledge on cc will be able to perform better in the pre and post surveys H3 – The story of the game will be a moderator in people’s engagement with climate related attitude (information &amp;amp; beliefs about climate change) -Survey will be used to develop game storyline, characters, and scenarios.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-10-18 | Meeting with Dr Balaji Kalluri</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-18/</guid>
      <description>In the soundboarding meeting with Dr Kalluri, Pralay team described the game.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-09-05 Meeting with Dr. Meghna Agarwala</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-09-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-09-04/</guid>
      <description>Different misinformation, what to focus on?</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-09-13 ELM Day 01</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-09-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-09-13/</guid>
      <description>Approach the ELM Team for clarifications about doubts, NDA, project requirements, any other needs.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-09-03 Meeting with Prof. Vijayraghavan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-09-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-09-03/</guid>
      <description>Identify age groups– look at what games are popular today (both entertainment and educational) Aspects of climate science that should or could be included– History of climate change – potentially make the game interactive Adaptation to climate change – game scenarios Mitigaton measures – game scenarios Keep everything that is minimal– simple and fun In terms of market, KVR cannot think of any example for climate game or interactive content which is not info dumpy.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-08-28 Interview</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-08-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-08-28/</guid>
      <description>Slide deck can be found here:</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-08-25 Team Meeting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-08-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-08-25/</guid>
      <description>Game World Another planet - world govt Climate Game Scenario: Are EVs really a “green” solution Game Narrative: # Concealed information regarding educational content of climate crisis/doomsday that gets revealed as the player plays the game.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-08-24 Team Meeting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-08-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-08-24/</guid>
      <description>Document the process of the ‘unconventional approach’ to science communication Set up a website with meeting notes Explore science communication evaluation framework Communications strategy: https://ssir.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024-08-23 Team Meeting</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-08-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-08-23/</guid>
      <description>Pointers to expand on:</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting Notes-abhishek</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-10-20/</guid>
      <description>Test notes</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
